<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Moonlight Arena</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="name_chel">Chelsea Manchenal</string>
    <string name="name_polly">Delfino de la Polly Wolly</string>
    <string name="name_con">Dr. Conphi Guuru</string>
    <string name="name_han">Hanie VI</string>
    <string name="name_excel">His Excellency</string>
    <string name="name_huy">Huy the Wise</string>
    <string name="name_aki">Minami-sama</string>
    <string name="name_ama">Panda Amanda</string>
    <string name="name_four">Pon van Four</string>
    <string name="name_kiel">Soo Jin Kiel</string>
    <string name="desc_chel">Business star of the English Premier League and an important voice of the UEFA who controls high shares of top tier clubs</string>
    <string name="desc_polly">Medals here, medals there, trophies almost everywhere. A truly sporting hero, the pride of Latin America</string>
    <string name="desc_con">Extremely obsessed with marsupials, the scientist built a large scale research institution in Australia and eventually the whole Oceania</string>
    <string name="desc_han">Hanie the Sixth, princess of fashions and arts in the Mediterranean. Along with her sister, she promotes the area most unique cultural values</string>
    <string name="desc_excel">Chairman of a colossal corporation in the United States who monopolizes many modern technologies and intellectual properties</string>
    <string name="desc_huy">A strategic advisor of South Vietnam who has sketched successful international development and investment plans for big corporations</string>
    <string name="desc_aki">Once a teenage idol and then grew to be a giant figure of the Japanese entertainment industry, the girl who shakes the entire Asian stock market</string>
    <string name="desc_ama">Prominent pioneer modern biomedical researcher in Taiwan who has hosted several international scientific seminars</string>
    <string name="desc_four">People call him "Knight of the Windmills" but hardly anyone in Netherlands know his true identity, a man who come in secret and leave in silence</string>
    <string name="desc_kiel">Popularly known as "national little sister" across South Korea, the young talent has pertained the title longer than any other celebrities</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">WelcomeActivity</string>
    <string name="bonus_mark">You have eliminated 90% of the opponents. The arena has reached its climax. Be careful, the top rivals are never easy to face</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rule">RuleActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bonus">BonusActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_victory">VictoryActivity</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg_1">Welcome to the Moonlight Arena</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg_2">It takes more than courage, intelligence, perserverance and luck to stand alone in this pressure</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg_3">Only the best few have conquered the moon and its precious treasure</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg_4">Could you be next?</string>
    <string name="rival_msg_1">the brightest stage shined by this moonlight</string>
    <string name="rival_msg_2">four secret shadows, the special challenge</string>
    <string name="rival_msg_3">you must overcome their ultimate brains to get to the highest prize</string>
    <string name="rival_msg_4">READY, and GOOD LUCK</string>
    <string name="end_msg">Unfortunately, you could not withstand the pressure of the Moonlight Arena. Only a few have ever come to see the glory of the moon</string>
    <string name="moon_piece_found_1">Wonderful!!! This is the first Moon Piece</string>
    <string name="moon_piece_found_2">Fantastic!!! You find the second Moon Piece, keep looking</string>
    <string name="moon_piece_found_3">Amazing!!! You have the third Moon Piece, more than half way to go</string>
    <string name="moon_piece_found_4">Brilliant!!! The fourth Moon Piece has been acquired, only one more to glory</string>
    <string name="moon_piece_found_5">Congratulation!!! All Moon Pieces have been found. The giant Moon Treasure is now assembled</string>
    <string name="victory_found_all_msg">This is a moment of history. You have found all Moon Pieces and assembled the Golden Moon. The ultimate treasure is now yours</string>
    <string name="victory_found_not_msg">Although you could not restore the Moon Treasure, your accomplishment will be remembered on the honored pillar of the Moonlight Arena</string>
    <string name="rival_view_instruct">Scroll the panel and click on guests to see more information</string>
    <string name="bonus_instruct">You have entered the secret tunnel under this arena, where the Moon Treasure is hidden. Use your golden keys to open those mysterious chests. Choose wisely, you can stop anytime. Remember that each gold key worths $250</string>
    <string name="rule_main_1">You must outsmart your opponents by answering questions correctly. Each round, $1000 (1000 pts) is distributed equally for each regular opponents; as they are removed from the game, you get their portions</string> 
    <string name="rule_main_2">If you surpass 90 regular opponents, you are prompted to a special level where you can use gold keys to open mysterious chests. Within the time limit, if you </string>
    <string name="rule_main_3">When you end your game with less than 90 rivals eliminated, you lose the battle and half of your pts (money) is taken away by rivals</string>
    <string name="rule_quest_1">Each question has 4 choices and falls under 1 of 8 topics. You have 20 seconds to answer; when time reaches 0, the moon explodes and your game ends</string>
    <string name="rule_quest_2">You have 3 helps: eliminating 2 wrong choices, changing question and polling the remaining opponents (you cannot poll the guests). Each can only be used once</string>
    <string name="rule_quest_3">Question is more difficult in later stages. After round 12, questions become extremely hard</string>
    <string name="rule_rival_1">There are 100 opponents and 4 special guests chosen randomly from a set of 10. There are three levels of opponents, first-time, experience and smart; which influence how they play and gain intelligence through out the game.</string>
    <string name="rule_rival_2">Guests are more intelligent than regular opponents and they each have 2 specialties. They rarely answer wrong on questions under their specialties</string>
    <string name="rule_rival_3">Each guests carries a unique ability. Upon defeating a guest, you acquire that ability, money and one gold key, which can be used for bonus round</string>
</resources>